A Guide to the Fillmore Norfleet Papers, 1940-1987
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Subject files., Extent: 14 boxes. (Box 4-17)
  - Subject Files - Part 4.
    - Cemeteries: Tombstone Inscriptions (Box 10, Folder 309)
    - Cemeteries: Tombstone Inscriptions (Box 10, Folder 310)
    - Churches: Clergymen (Box 10, Folder 311)
    - Churches: Grace [Ca Ira] Church, Cumberland (Box 10, Folder 312)
    - Churches: Upper Parish Church Processioning Precincts (Box 10, Folder 313)
    - Churches: Upper Parish Vestry Book, Abstracts (Box 10, Folder 314)
    - Churches: Program unveiling tablets at site of First Church in Suffolk, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 315)
    - Churches: Methodist Church (Box 10, Folder 316)
    - Churches: Quaker Records (Box 10, Folder 317)
    - Churches: Quaker Records [Chuckatuck Monthly Meeting transcript] (Box 10, Folder 318-219)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Jennie Parker Ballard Diaries, 1865 (Box 10, Folder 320)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Jennie Parker Ballard Letters [copies, calendar, index] ca. 1834-1877 (Box 10, Folder 321)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Jennie Parker Ballard Letters, ca. 1834-1877 [notes] (Box 10, Folder 322)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Jennie Parker Ballard Letters, ca. 1834-1877 (Box 10, Folder 323)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Alida Norfleet Beamon Letters, 1868-1877 (Box 10, Folder 324)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Brent - Daniel Letters, 1839-1840 (Box 10, Folder 325)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Dawson Letters, 1818 (Box 10, Folder 326)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Godwin Letters, 1848 (Box 10, Folder 327)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Keeling-Fisher Letters, 1817 (Box 10, Folder 328)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Journal of Abigail Langley, 1660-1815 (Box 11, Folder 329)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Lewis Letters, 1850-51 (Box 11, Folder 330)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Murdaugh Letter, 1816 (Box 11, Folder 331)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Hamlin L. Norfleet Letters, 1867-69, 1910-14 (Box 11, Folder 332)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Reminiscences of Robert Jethro Norfleet, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 333)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Norfleet Family Letters and Accounts, ca. 1861-1873 (Box 11, Folder 334)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Joseph Prentis Account book, 1817-1834 (Box 11, Folder 335)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Joseph Prentis Account Book [additions] (Box 11, Folder 336)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Prentis Letters, 1805 (Box 11, Folder 337)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Prentis Letters, 1854 (Box 11, Folder 338)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Prentis Transcripts, ca. 1805-1818 (Box 11, Folder 339)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: James A. Riddick Journal, 1833-1847 (Box 11)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: James A. Riddick Diary, 1836-1849 (Box 11, Folder 341)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: James A. Riddick Reminiscences, 1880 (Box 11, Folder 342)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Josiah Riddick, Jr., Account Book, 1805-1835 (Box 11, Folder 343)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Josiah H. Riddick Account Book, 1798-1810 (Box 11, Folder 344)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Richard W. Riddick Letters, 1818-1827 (Box 11, Folder 345-346)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Robert Moore Riddick Letters, 1817-1828 (Box 11, Folder 347)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Thomas Fiveash Riddick and Richard W. Riddick Letters, ca. 1820-1824 (Box 11, Folder 348)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Thomas F. Riddick Letters, 1824 (Box 11, Folder 349)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Riddick Correspondence, 1844, 186- (Box 11, Folder 350)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: French Embassy Correspondence, 1825 (Box 11, Folder 351)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: St. Paul's Church, Suffolk, Ladies Sewing Circle Record (Box 11, Folder 352)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: UVA Proctor's Papers, 1837-1855 (Box 11, Folder 353)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: UVA Proctor's Papers, 1841-1844 (Box 11, Folder 354)
    - Land Records: Beamon Land [Abstract of Title] (Box 11, Folder 355)
    - Land Records: "Retreat Farm" [Abstract of Titles] (Box 11, Folder 356)
    - Land Records: Abstract of Titles [J. R. Kilby Papers] (Box 11, Folder 357-359)
    - Land Records: Kilby Deed and Title Abstracts (Box 11, Folder 360)
    - Land Records: Nansemond Co. Deeds, ca. 1722-1871 (Box 11, Folder 361)
    - Land Records: Nansemond Co. Deed Abstracts, 1722-1881 (Box 11, Folder 362)
    - Land Records: Nansemond Co. Deed Abstracts, ca. 1856-1881 (Box 11, Folder 363)
    - Land Records: Nansemond Co. Deeds Conveying Land in the Upper Parish, 1722-1853 (Box 11, Folder 364)
    - Land Records: Deeds [Nansemond Co., Norfolk Co., VA; Gates Co., NC, ca. 1704-1883 (Box 11, Folder 365)
    - Land Records: Nansemond Co. Deed Abstracts [includes abstracts of title, wills] ca. 1815-1860 (Box 11, Folder 366)
    - Land Records: Gates Co., NC, Deeds, ca. 1776-1808 (Box 11, Folder 367)
    - Land Records: Gates Co., NC Deeds and Wills, 1784-1807 (Box 11, Folder 368)
    - Land Records: Nansemond Co. Land Patents, 1666-1673 (Box 11, Folder 369)
    - Land Records: Nansemond Co. Land Patents, ca. 1637-1727 (Box 11, Folder 370)
    - Land Records: Nansemond Co. Patents, 1635-1713 (Box 11, Folder 371)
    - Land Records: Nansemond Co. Patents, ca. 1643-1767 (Box 11, Folder 372)
    - Land Records: Land Patents, A-F, ca. 1634-1727 (including biographies) (Box 11, Folder 373)
    - Land Records: Land Patents, G-N, ca. 1634-1727 (including biographies) (Box 11, Folder 374)
    - Land Records: Land Patents, O-Y, ca. 1634-1727 (including biographies) (Box 11, Folder 375)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Dawson Letters (Box 12, Folder 376)
    - Diaries, Letters, Account Books: Reminiscences of Suffolk by James A. Riddick, 1880 (Box 12, Folder 377)
    - Land Records: Land Grants [Re: Deeds from J. R. Kilby Papers, ca. 1638-1868 (Box 13, Folder 378)
    - Land Records: Nansemond Co. Land Patents, ca. 1637-1767 (Box 13, Folder 379)
    - Land Records: Nansemond Co. Patents (indexed transcripts, ca. 1666-1868 (Box 13, Folder 380)
    - Land Records: Patents and Processioner's abstracts, ca. 1683-1804 (Box 13, Folder 381)
    - Land Records: J. H. Granbery Notes, Patents/Plats, ca. 1635-1804 (Box 13, Folder 382)
    - Land Records: Quit Rent Roll, 1704 (Box 13, Folder 383-384)
    - Land Records: Nansemond Co. Land, Tax List, 1782-1836 (Box 13, Folder 385)
    - Land Records: Nansemond Co. Land, Tax List, 1783-1843 (Box 13, Folder 386)
    - Land Records: Suffolk Lot Tax Lists, 1782-1836 (Box 13, Folder 387)
    - Land Records: Suffolk Lot Tax Lists, ca. 1782-1861 (Box 13, Folder 388)
    - Land Records: Washington, Walker & Co. Land Tax Lists, ca. 1838-1858 (Box 13, Folder 389)
    - Land Records: Washington, Walker & Co. Land Tax Lists, ca. 1819-1858 (Box 13, Folder 390)
    - Land Records: Dismal Swamp Ownership (Box 13, Folder 391)
    - Land Records: The Dividing Line [VA-NC boundary] (Box 13, Folder 392)
    - Land Records: Thomas Rustin's Land (Box 13, Folder 393)
    - Land Records: Norfleet-Washington Lands (Box 13, Folder 394)
    - Land Records: George Washington's [Nansemond Co.] Land (Box 13, Folder 395)
    - Land Records: Washington, Walker & Co. Land (Box 13, Folder 396)
    - Land Records: A Record of Farms & Their Owners in Lower Parish of Nansemond Co. by William Turner Jordan (Box 13, Folder 397)
    - Lots: Suffolk Lot Owners, 1782-1789 (Box 13, Folder 398)
    - Lots: Plats of Suffolk Lots & Owners (Box 13, Folder 399)
    - Lots: Suffolk Lots Sold at Public Auction, 1791 (Box 13, Folder 400)
    - Lots: Suffolk Lots (Box 13, Folder 401-403)
    - Lots: Suffolk Lots, Plats and Owners (Box 13, Folder 404)
    - Lots: Notes on Lots in Old Town (Box 13, Folder 405)
    - Lots: Lot Owners on Main Street, Suffolk [Brownie Riddick (Mrs. Henry A. Rawles) memory] (Box 13, Folder 406)
    - Lots: Plat of Lot Owners on Main Street, Suffolk (Box 13, Folder 407)
    - Lots: Suffolk Lots, 1-3 [9], [78], 79 (Box 13, Folder 408)
    - Lots: Suffolk Lots, Owen Flynn to Bank Street (Box 13, Folder 409)
    - Lots: Suffolk Lots, Holland Lot, Christian Church Lot (Box 13, Folder 410)
    - Lots: Suffolk Lots, New Town (Box 13, Folder 411)
    - Lots: Suffolk Lots, New Town Lot Owners (Box 13, Folder 412)
    - Lots: Maps for New Town (Box 13, Folder 413)
    - Lots: Lots in Suffolk (Box 13, Folder 414)
    - Marriage Records: Nansemond County Marriage Registers, Nos. 1-3, 1866-1921 (Box 13, Folder 415)
    - Marriage Records: Suffolk City, Nansemond Co., Marriage Register Abstracts, ca. 1867-1918 (Box 13, Folder 416)
    - Marriage Records: Suffolk Marriages & Wills, 1910-1916 (Box 13, Folder 417)
    - Marriage Records: Norfolk Co. Marriage Records, 1744-1817 (Box 13, Folder 418)
    - Marriage Records: Isle of Wight Co., Nansemond Co.; Gates Co., NC Marriages ca. 1628-1866 (Box 13, Folder 419)
    - Marriage Records: Nansemond Co., Isle of Wight Co., Southampton Co.; Gates Co., NC Marriages, ca. 1628-1875 (Box 13, Folder 420)
    - Marriage Records: Sussex Co., Southampton Co. Marriages, 1771-1851 (Box 13, Folder 421)
    - Military Records: Samuel Carr Revolutionary War Claims (Box 14, Folder 422)
    - Military Records: Abram Cole Revolutionary War Service (Box 14, Folder 423)
    - Military Records: Nathaniel Norfleet Revolutionary War Pension Application (Box 14, Folder 424)
    - Military Records: Jason Riddick Commission and Resignation 1778, 1781 (Box 14, Folder 425)
    - Military Records: Willis Riddick Revolutionary War Service, petition by executor, Nathaniel Riddick (Box 14, Folder 426)
    - Military Records: Revolutionary War Vol. I (Box 14, Folder 427-428)
    - Military Records: Revolutionary Soldiers, folder 1 (Box 14, Folder 429)
    - Military Records: Revolutionary Soldiers, folder 2 (Box 14, Folder 430)
    - Military Records: Revolutionary War, Nansemond Soldiers (Box 14, Folder 431-432)
    - Military Records: Revolutionary War, [Riddick, Nansemond Co. Soldiers] (Box 14, Folder 433)
    - Military Records: Revolutionary War, Nansemond Co. Soldiers (Box 14, Folder 434-435)
    - Military Records: Revolutionary War, Legislative Petitions (Box 14, Folder 436)
    - Military Records: Revolutionary War, Bounty Warrants (Box 14, Folder 437)
    - Military Records: Revolutionary War, Bounty Warrants, Pensions (Box 14, Folder 438)
    - Military Records: Revolutionary War, Bounty Warrants (Box 14, Folder 439)
    - Military Records: Revolutionary War, Orderly Book of the 4th VA Regiment (Box 14, Folder 440-441)
    - Military Records: Revolutionary War, MacClenny's Scrapbook (Box 14, Folder 442)
    - Military Records: Revolutionary War, Va Soldiers of 1776 (Box 14, Folder 443)
    - Military Records: Revolutionary War, Virginia's Navy (Box 14, Folder 444)
    - Military Records: Revolutionary War, Losses Sustained by British (Box 14, Folder 445-446)
    - Military Records: Revolutionary War, Public Service Claims (Box 14, Folder 447-448)
    - Military Records: Revolutionary War, Pension Applications (Box 14, Folder 449)
    - Military Records: Revolutionary War/War of 1812, Pension Applications (Box 14, Folder 450)
    - Military Records: War of 1812, Nansemond Co. Bounty Claims, Pay Rolls (Box 14, Folder 451)
    - Military Records: Biographies of Soldiers (Box 14, Folder 452)
    - Military Records: Civil War (Box 14, Folder 453)
    - Military Records: Reports of Maj. Gen. John J. Peck, 1862-1863 (Box 14, Folder 454)
    - Mutual Assurance Society: Nansemond Co. Policy Abstracts, ca. 1802-1807 (Box 14, Folder 455)
    - Mutual Assurance Society: Nansemond Co. Policy Abstracts, ca. 1802-1811 (Box 14, Folder 456)
    - Mutual Assurance Society: Nansemond Co. Policy Abstracts, ca. 1796-1819 [includes Suffolk, Isle of Wight] (Box 14, Folder 457)
    - Mutual Assurance Society: Suffolk Abstracts, ca. 1796-1846 (Box 14, Folder 458)
    - Mutual Assurance Society: Abstracts, ca. 1796-1846 (Box 14, Folder 459)
    - Mutual Assurance Society: Abstracts [Suffolk, Norfolk, Richmond], ca. 1818-1854 (Box 14, Folder 460)
    - Mutual Assurance Society: Index to Nansemond Co. Policies, ca. 1796-1821 (Box 14, Folder 461)
    - Mutual Assurance Society: Index to Policies, Abstracts, ca. 1796-1859 (Box 14, Folder 462)
    - Newspapers: Obituaries and Marriage Notices ca. 1753-1982 (Box 15, Folder 463)
    - Newspapers: Marriages and Obituaries from Richmond Newspapers, ca. 1739-1820 (Box 15, Folder 464)
    - Newspapers: Norfolk Gazette abstracts, 1804-1806 (Box 15, Folder 465)
    - Newspapers: State Gazette photostats, 1789 (Box 15, Folder 466)
    - Newspapers: Suffolk Herald obituaries, abstracts, ca. 1879-1880 (Box 15, Folder 467)
    - Newspapers: Suffolk Herald, Christian Sun abstracts, ca. 1847-1900 (Box 15, Folder 468)
    - Newspapers: Virginia Gazette abstracts, ca. 1736-1789 (Box 15, Folder 469)
    - Newspapers: Lists of Newspapers (Box 15, Folder 470)
    - Places: Bracketts [Louisa Co.] (Box 15, Folder 471)
    - Places: Bunting Farm, Gun Landing, Tucker's Neck (Box 15, Folder 472)
    - Places: Confederate Settlements in Brazil (Box 15, Folder 473)
    - Places: Dismal Swamp (Box 15, Folder 474)
    - Places: Dunlora [includes Carr Family] (Box 15, Folder 475-476)
    - Places: England (Box 15, Folder 477)
    - Places: Four Mile Tree (Box 15, Folder 478)
    - Places: Heacham, England (Box 15, Folder 479)
    - Places: Kent, England (Box 15, Folder 480)
    - Places: Louisiana (Box 15, Folder 481)
    - Places: Meade's Mill (Box 15, Folder 482)
    - Places: Michie Tavern (Box 15, Folder 483)
    - Places: Nansemond Co. Mills (Box 15, Folder 484)
    - Places: National Bank of Suffolk (Box 15, Folder 485)
    - Places: Read's Ferry (Box 15, Folder 486)
    - Places: Rich Square, NC (Box 15, Folder 487)
    - Places: Pigeon Hill (Box 15, Folder 488)
    - Places: Richmond City [includes Beaux-Arts, St. Memin research] (Box 15, Folder 489)
    - Places: Rocky Mills [includes Syme Family] (Box 15, Folder 490)
    - Places: Spring Hill (Box 15, Folder 491)
    - Places: Suffolk [establishment, early history] (Box 15, Folder 492)
    - Places: New Town, Suffolk (Box 15, Folder 493)
    - Places: Suffolk Military Academy (Box 15, Folder 494)
    - Places: Sussex Co. (Box 15, Folder 495)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: List of Administrators, 1789-1814 [Nansemond Co.] (Box 15, Folder 496)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Census, 1790 [1783-1785] [Nansemond Co.] (Box 15, Folder 497)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Census, 1783, 1820, 1830 [Nansemond Co.] (Box 15, Folder 498)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Census, index, 1820, 1830 [Nansemond Co.] (Box 15, Folder 499)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Census, 1820, 1830 [Nansemond Co.] (Box 15, Folder 500)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Census, 1850 [vols. 1-5] [Nansemond Co.] (Box 15, Folder 501)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Census, 1850 [vols. 6-99] [Nansemond Co.] (Box 15, Folder 502)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Census, 1860 [Nansemond Co.] (Box 15, Folder 503)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Deed/Will Transcriptions, 1731-1939 [Nansemond Co.] (Box 15, Folder 504)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Lists of Executors, 1789-1814 [Nansemond Co.] (Box 15, Folder 505)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Fee Books, 1789-1814 [Nansemond Co.] (Box 15, Folder 506-507)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Guardian Appointments, 1789-1814 [Nansemond Co] (Box 16, Folder 508)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Legislative Petitions, 1778-1830 [Nansemond Co.] (Box 16, Folder 509-511)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: John R. Kilby's Commission Book, 1849-1866, n.d. [Nansemond Co.] (Box 16, Folder 512)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Wills, 1653-1908 [Nansemond Co.] (Box 16, Folder 513)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Wills, ca. 1677-1928 [Nansemond Co.] (Box 16, Folder 514)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Legal Papers [abstracts from J. R. Kilby, Webb-Prentis Co. Records, 1665-1874 [Nansemond Co.] (Box 16, Folder 515)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Wills, ca. 1693-1800 [Elizabeth City Co.] and ca. 1765-1823 [Crozier] (Box 16, Folder 516)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Wills, 1726-1773> [Norfolk Co.] (Box 16, Folder 517)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Record Abstracts, 1671-1742 [Surry Co.] (Box 16, Folder 518)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Calendar of State Papers, 1781-1813 (Box 16, Folder 519)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Executive Journals, 1680-1790 (Box 16, Folder 520)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Henings Statutes at Large, 1642/3-1818 (Box 16, Folder 521)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Notes from Legal Cases, 1743-1833 [Nansemond Co.] (Box 16, Folder 522)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Supreme Court/General Court Cases, 1805-1844 (Box 16, Folder 523)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Colonial Papers (Box 16, Folder 524)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Colonial Papers II (Box 16, Folder 525)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Deed/Will Transcripts, 1779-1815 [Gates Co., NC] (Box 16, Folder 526)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: Tax List, 1784 [Hertford Co., NC] (Box 16, Folder 527)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: North Carolina Wills, 1680-1777 (Box 16, Folder 528)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: NC Historical and Genealogical Register abstracts, 1682-1849 (Box 16, Folder 529)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: NC Historical and Genealogical Register abstracts, 1673-1864 (Box 16, Folder 530)
    - Wills and Abstracts of Legal Records: NC Historical and Genealogical Register abstracts, ca. 1689-1866 (Box 16, Folder 531)
    - Kilby Papers: Index (Box 16, Folder 532)
    - Kilby Papers: Abstracts, 1848-1869 (Box 16, Folder 533)
    - Kilby Papers: Abstracts, ca. 1764-1866 (Box 16, Folder 534)
    - Kilby Papers: Abstracts, 1711-1875 (Box 16, Folder 535)
    - Kilby Papers: Index to Wills (Box 16, Folder 536)
    - Webb-Prentis Papers: Annotated Copies of Letters, 1805-1843, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 537)
    - Webb-Prentis Papers: Transcripts (Box 16, Folder 538)
    - Webb-Prentis Papers: Abstracts (Box 16, Folder 539-542)
    - Webb-Prentis Papers: Notes on Letters (Box 16, Folder 543)
    - Webb-Prentis Papers: Index (Box 16, Folder 544)
    - Miscellaneous: Art [Used Notes] folder 1 (Box 16, Folder 545)
    - Miscellaneous: Art [Used Notes] folder 2 (Box 16, Folder 546)
    - Miscellaneous: Care and Editing of Manuscripts (Box 17, Folder 547)
    - Miscellaneous: W. A. Crozier, Heraldic Abstracts (Box 17, Folder 548)
    - Miscellaneous: List of Daguerreotypes (Box 17, Folder 549)
    - Miscellaneous: Doctors [Colonial NC] (Box 17, Folder 550)
    - Miscellaneous: Colonial and State Political History of Hertford Co., NC (Box 17, Folder 551)
    - Miscellaneous: Invitations, Cards (Box 17, Folder 552)
    - Miscellaneous: Lafayette's Return Visit to America (Box 17, Folder 553)
    - Miscellaneous: Miscellaneous Records [fell out of books in Fillmore Norfleet's Library] (Box 17, Folder 554)
    - Miscellaneous: Notebook 1 (Box 17, Folder 555)
    - Miscellaneous: Notebook 2 (Box 17, Folder 556)
    - Miscellaneous: Notebook 3 (Box 17, Folder 557)
    - Miscellaneous: Notebook 4 (Box 17, Folder 558)
    - Miscellaneous: Lists of Officeholders, 1639-1890 (Box 17, Folder 559)
    - Miscellaneous: Life and Labor in the Old South (Box 17, Folder 560)
    - Miscellaneous: Portraits (Box 17, Folder 561)
    - Miscellaneous: A Rainbow Festival, 1887 (Box 17, Folder 562)
    - Miscellaneous: Random Notes (Box 17, Folder 563-568)
    - Miscellaneous: Adventures of a Young Englishman (Box 17, Folder 569)
    - Miscellaneous: Subscription and List of Stockholders on Steamer Star> (Box 17, Folder 570)
    - Miscellaneous: Suffolk Mace (Box 17, Folder 571)
    - Bibliography (Box 17, Folder 572-573)
    - Map Bibliography (Box 17, Folder 574)
    - Virginia Historical Society Bibliography (Box 17, Folder 575)
    - Nansemond County Bibliography (Box 17, Folder 576)
    - Revolutionary War/Colonial Bibliographies (Box 17, Folder 577)
- Series III. Legal documents., Extent: 1 box. (Box 18)
  The items in this section of the Fillmore Norfleet Papers are photocopies of original records or extant copies of original records. They are arranged by record group and then chronologically.
  - Bonds, 1792-1793. (Box 18, Folder 578)
  - Court Papers, 1762, 1790, 1797, 1827-1828, 1831, 1835, 1837, 1843, 1848-1849, 1877, 1887, 1897, 1969. (Box 18, Folder 579)
  - Deeds, 1734, 1736, 1746, 1762, 1767, 1772, 1788. (Box 18, Folder 580)
  - Deeds, 1804, 1806, 1815, 1817, 1832, 1835, 1840, 1842-1844, 1848-1849, 1852, 1860, 1862, 1866, 1872, 1943. (Box 18, Folder 581)
  - Fiduciary Records, 1782, 1789, 1801, 1839, 1856-1860, 1874, 1889. (Box 18, Folder 582)
  - Marriage Records, 1779, 1819, (1820?). (Box 18, Folder 583)
  - Overseer of the Poor Papers, 1843. (Box 18, Folder 584)
  - Patent, 1763. (Box 18, Folder 585)
  - Plats, 1765, 1856, 1919, 1966, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 586)
  - Power of Attorney, 1801. (Box 18, Folder 587)
  - School Expenses, 1833. (Box 18, Folder 588)
  - Wills, 1662, 1680. (Box 18, Folder 589)
  - Wills, 1752, 1767, 1776-1777, 1779, 1782-1783, 1789, 1791, 1795. (Box 18, Folder 590)
  - Wills, 1803, 1809, 1820, 1822-1823, 1825, 1830, 1840-1843, 1855, 1857-1858, 1864-1865, 1869. (Box 18, Folder 591)
- Series IV. Printed materials., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 19-21)
  This portion of the Fillmore Norfleet Papers consists of early drafts of his works relating to Nansemond County. Some of the folders contain material which seems to have been the earliest stages of what eventually appeared in print and have, therefore, been included in the Printed Materials portion of the collection. In addition to drafts, there are copies of Mr. Norfleet's books which have been annotated by him. There are also published genealogical works and record abstracts which contain annotations by Mr. Norfleet.
  - Elisha Norfleet [draft] (Box 19, Folder 592)
  - Elisha Norfleet [additions to be made] (Box 19, Folder 593)
  - Elisha Norfleet [annotated copy] (Box 19, Folder 594)
  - Bible Records of Suffolk and Nansemond Co. [early draft, part 1] (Box 19, Folder 595)
  - Bible Records of Suffolk and Nansemond Co. [early draft, part 2] (Box 19, Folder 596)
  - Bible Records of Suffolk and Nansemond Co. [rough draft] (Box 19, Folder 597)
  - Bible Records of Suffolk and Nansemond Co. [duplicate manuscript] (Box 19, Folder 598)
  - In Britain Lies Virginia [manuscript] (Box 19, Folder 599)
  - Notes for James Andrew Riddick's Reminiscences of Suffolk (1880) (Box 20, Folder 600)
  - Suffolk in Virginia [early working notes] (Box 20, Folder 601)
  - Main Street Lots: Tenants Vol. I [A-Cl] (Box 20, Folder 602)
  - Main Street Lots: Tenants Vol. I [Co-Hall] (Box 20, Folder 603)
  - Main Street Lots: Tenants Vol. I [Han-Nel] (Box 20, Folder 604)
  - Main Street Lot Owners Suffolk Lots and Lives [first draft] Vol. II [N-R] (Box 20, Folder 605)
  - Main Street Lot Owners Suffolk Lots and Lives [S-W, picture] (Box 20, Folder 606)
  - Suffolk Citizens: Their Lots and Lives [A-Bu] (Box 20, Folder 607)
  - Suffolk Citizens: Their Lots and Lives [Ca-Du] (Box 20, Folder 608)
  - Suffolk Citizens: Their Lots and Lives [E-Hod] (Box 20, Folder 609)
  - Suffolk Citizens: Their Lots and Lives [Hol-Mer] (Box 20, Folder 610)
  - Suffolk Citizens: Their Lots and Lives [Met-Pugh] (Box 20, Folder 611)